<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
<title>Looptid.com</title>
<link rel="self" href="http://looptid.com/lyrics-atom.xml"/>
<link href="http://looptid.com/"/>
<id>http://looptid.com/lyrics-atom.xml</id>
<updated>2006-06-06T01:00:51+00:00</updated>
<entry xml:lang="en-us">
  <title type="html">The Humpty Dance</title>
  <link href="http://looptid.com/"/>
  <id>http://looptid.com/</id>
  <updated>2006-06-05T16:30:51+00:00</updated>
  <content type="xhtml">
<div xmlns="http://www.w3.org/1999/xhtml">
<h4><a name="verseone">Verse One</a></h4>
<pre>
All right!
Stop whatcha doin'
'cause I'm about to ruin
the image and the style that ya used to.
I look funny,
but yo I'm makin' money, see
so yo world I hope you're ready for me.
Now gather round
I'm the new fool in town
and my sound's laid down by the Underground.
I drink up all the <a href="http://www.hennessy-cognac.com/">Hennessy</a> ya got on ya shelf
so just <a href="http://moore.cx/dan/">let me introduce myself</a>
My name is Humpty, pronounced with a Umpty.
Yo ladies, oh how I <a href="http://www.mastersandjohnson.com/">like to hump</a> thee.
And all the rappers in the <a href="http://www.billboard.com/billboard/charts/airplay/rap.jsp">top ten</a>--please allow me to bump thee.
I'm steppin' tall, y'all,
and just like Humpty Dumpty
you're gonna fall when the <a href="http://www.usa.denon.com/">stereos</a> pump me.
I like to rhyme,  
I like my beats funky,
<a href="http://www.ettlinc.com/Svesco.htm">I'm spunky</a>.  I like my <a href="http://www.quakeroats.com/qfb_OurBrands/Quaker/BreakfastCereals/QuakerOatmealCereal.cfm">oatmeal</a> lumpy.
I'm sick wit dis, straight gangsta mack
but sometimes I get ridiculous
I'll eat up all your <a href="http://www.manischewitz.com/">crackers</a> and your licorice
hey yo fat girl, c'mere--are ya ticklish?
Yeah, I called ya <q>fat</q>.
<a href="http://maddox.xmission.com/subway.html">Look at me, I'm skinny</a>
It never stopped me from gettin' busy
I'm a freak 
I like the girls with the boom
I once got busy in a <a href="http://www.burgerking.com/">Burger King</a> bathroom
I'm crazy.
Allow me to amaze thee.
They say I'm ugly but it just don't faze me.
I'm still gettin' in the girls' pants
and I even got my own dance
</pre>

<h4><a name="chorus">Chorus</a></h4>
<pre>
The Humpty Dance is your chance to do the Hump
Do the Humpty Hump, come on and do the Humpty Hump
Do the Humpty Hump, just watch me do the Humpty Hump
Do ya know what I'm doin', doin' the Humpty Hump
Do the Humpty Hump, do the Humpty Hump
</pre>

<h4><a name="versetwo">Verse Two</a></h4>
<pre>
People say <q>Yo, Humpty, you're really funny lookin'</q>
that's all right 'cause I get things cookin'
Ya stare, ya glare, ya constantly try to compare me
but ya can't get near me
I give 'em more, see, and on the floor, B,
all the <a href="http://www.greedygirl.com/">girls</a> they adore me
Oh yes, ladies, I'm really bein' sincere
'cause in a 69 my Humpty nose will tickle ya rear. 
My nose is big, uh-uh I'm not ashamed
Big like a pickle, I'm still gettin' paid
I get laid by the ladies, ya know I'm in charge,
both how I'm livin' and my nose is large
I get stoopid, I shoot an arrow like Cupid,
I use a word that don't mean nothin', like <q><a href="http://looptid.com/">looptid</a></q>
I sang on <a href="http://www.amazon.com/exec/obidos/ASIN/B000000HHM">Doowutchyalike</a>, and if ya missed it,
I'm the one who said just <q>grab 'em in the biscuits</q>
Also told ya that I like to bite
Well, yeah, I guess it's obvious, I also like to write.
All ya had to do was give Humpty a chance 
and now I'm gonna do my dance.
</pre>

<p>{ <a href="#chorus">Chorus</a> }</p>

<h4>Breakdown</h4>
<pre>
Oh, yeah, that's the break, y'all
Let me hear a little bit of that bass groove right here
Oh, yeah!
Now that I told ya a little bit about myself
let me tell ya a little bit about this dance
It's real easy to do--check it out
</pre>

<h4><a name="versethree">Verse Three</a></h4>

<pre>
First I limp to the side like my leg was broken
Shakin' and twitchin' kinda like I was smokin'
Crazy wack funky
People say <q>ya look like <a href="http://www.mchammerusa.com/">M.C. Hammer</a> on crack, Humpty</q>
That's all right 'cause my body's in motion
It's supposed to look like a fit or a convulsion
Anyone can play this game
This is my dance, y'all, Humpty Hump's my name
No two people will do it the same
Ya got it down when ya appear to be in pain
Humpin', funkin', jumpin',
jig around, shakin' ya rump,
and when the dude a chump pump points a finger like a stump
tell him <q>step off, I'm doin' the Hump</q>
</pre>

<p>{ <a href="#chorus">Chorus</a> }</p>

<pre>
Black people, do the Humpty Hump, do the Humpty Hump
White people, do the Humpty Hump, do the Humpty Hump
<a href="http://welcome.topuertorico.org/">Puerto Ricans</a>, do the Humpty Hump, just keep on doin' the Hump
<a href="http://www.ipacific.com/samoa/samoa.html">Samoans</a>, do the Humpty Hump, do the Humpty Hump

Let's get <a href="http://www.stupid.com/">stoopid</a>!
</pre>

<p>{ <a href="#chorus">Chorus</a> }</p>

<pre>
Oh, yeah, come on and break it down
</pre>

<h4>Outro</h4>

<pre>
Once again, the Underground is in the house
I'd like to send a shout out to the whole world,
keep on doin' the Humpty Dance,
and to the ladies,
peace and Humptiness forever

{ Music and fade }
</pre>
</div>
  </content>
  <author>
    <name>Looptid.com</name>
    <uri>http://looptid.com/</uri>
  </author>
</entry>
</feed>
